shuttersalt.com 2011-06-07

# Privacy Policy | ShutterSalt

This privacy policy (“the Policy”) governs the website Shuttersalt, found at www.shuttersalt.com (the “Site”). By using the Site, you agree to the terms of the Policy.

Your privacy is important to us. As a general matter, Shuttersalt does not automatically collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, or other contact information. Shuttersalt only requests such personal information when users request information from Shuttersalt or otherwise communicate with Shuttersalt. We use such personal information only for these specific purposes. Shuttersalt may also automatically collect certain nonpersonal information (such as the identity of your web browser, the type of operating system you use, your IP address or the domain name of your Internet service provider) to help us understand how our readers use the Site. We use this information for internal purposes only, such as to evaluate site use, assess and improve site performance, and improve the content of the Site.

Shuttersalt will keep your information confidential and will not provide your information to any third party. Shuttersalt does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

Shuttersalt may disclose personal information in special situations where Shuttersalt has reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injurying or interfering with Shuttersalt’s rights. Shuttersalt may also reveal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

Shuttersalt may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. Shuttersalt does not control such other sites and is not responsible for their content or their privacy policies. Shuttersalt’s inclusion of such links does not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites

or of their owners or operators.

Shuttersalt reserves the right to modify the Policy at any time. We will post a copy of the policy as modified on the Site. You may wish to check the Policy periodically to determine whether it has been modified.
